

Contact

+48 601 914 103



raffal.kozlowski@gmail.com

Software & Languages

HTML 40%

CSS

JavaScript

GIT

English

Soft Skills

Scrum

50%

Kanban

Attention to details

Communication

Additional activities

- PRINCE2 Foundation accredited course with exam on foundation grade
- Implementing Kanban methodology for project management team in OPG Property Professionals
- Implementing advanced MS Outlook task functions for project management team in OPG Property Professionals

Interests

- Martial Arts 1 Dan Traditional Karate grade
- · Healthy lifestyle and personal growth

Rafał Kozłowski

Project manager, intent to become a software engineer.

From some time I am preparing for career path change into software engineering. I believe that my engineering education, solid project management and customer relations experience will help me to develop new set of skills quickly and make profound impact on the quality of my work.

What excites me the most in coding? How fast and simply you can transform the word into visual, dynamic objects. How you can create something out of nothing. How programs, websites and apps makes life easier for people all over the world.

Solving problems and finding new ways to deliver solution gives me a feeling of development, fullfilment and personal growth. That is why I am determined to become the part of IT world.

Education & courses

Front-End Engineer, Codecademy / Online course

Git and GitHub from scratch, UDEMY / Online course

Basics of HTML and CSS, GolT / 6-day online marathon

Front-End Developer, Software Development Academy / Online course

Project management, Technical University of Lodz / Postgraduate studies 2018 - 2019

Civil engineering, Technical University of Lodz / Master's degree

2013 - 2016

Civil engineering, Technical University of Lodz / Bachelor's degree

2009 - 2013

Employment history

Co-owner at P.W. RED s.c.

2020 - up to now

- Execution of ventilation and gas installation audits
- · Preparing offers and formal documentation
- · Contact with clients

Senior Project Manager at OPG Property Professionals

2018 - 2020

- · Project Management Team coordination
- · Coordination of design and realization stage of property investments
- · Contact with consultants
- · Negotiations with contractors
- · Investments' budget creation
- Substantive and financial control of the projects

Investor Supervision Inspector at University of Lodz

2017

- · Investments' budget creation
- · Coordination of design stage of property investments
- · Substantive and financial control of the projects

Cost Estimator/ Site engineer at Joka Sp. z o.o.

2015 - 2017

- · Creation of construction cost estimate
- · Contact and negotiations with investors and contractors

Site engineer at SKANSKA S.A.

2014 - 2015

- · Controlling concrete and ground works
- · Reporting to Site Manager
- · Negotiations with contractors